A Guide to the Bruce Family Papers 1746-1905, n.d.
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Bruce Family Papers, 1746-1905, n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
2692
This holding consists of ca. 330 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This item was acquired as a gift on December 16, 1963.
Scope and Content Information
Correspondence, journals, and account books of James Bruce and his son, James Cole Bruce, of Berry Hill, Halifax County. There are lists of slaves, e.g., a November 22, 1849, list and inventory of slaves on the plantation of Messrs. Bruce, Seddon, and Williams and an 1852 "Register of Negroes," plus many entries in the account books and other material relating to slavery.
Contents List
- Indentures of James Hunt, Dannitt Abney, William Light, William Younger, James Bruce 1746-1800 (Box 1)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1790 (Box 1)
- Indenture between Isaac Coles and James Bruce May 28, 1792 (Box 1)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1796 (Box 1)
- Isaac A. Coles to Henry St. George Tucker July 20, 1799 (Box 1)
- Indentures of James Bruce 1800-1810 (Box 1)
- Indentures of Bruce and Sydnor 1800-1819 (Box 1)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1802-1813, 9 folders (Box 1)
- Indentures between James Grant and Bruce and Easley August 27, 1814 (Box 1)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1814 (Box 1)
- Indentures of Bruce and Easley 1814-1832 (Box 1)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1815-1817 (Box 1)
- Indentures of Bruce and Hagood 1817-1819 (Box 2)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1818 (Box 2)
- Charles B. Williams to James Bruce July 13, 1819 (Box 2)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1819-1820, 2 folders (Box 2)
- Indentures of Bruce and Sydnor 1820-1835 (Box 2)
- Deeds of Trust of James Bruce 1820-1842 (Box 2)
- James Madison to James Bruce October 20, 1821 (Box 2)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1821-1822, 2 folders (Box 2)
- James Bruce's Commission as Sheriff of Halifax County 1822-1823 (Box 2)
- Business Papers of James Bruce 1823 (Box 2)
- James C. Bruce to James Bruce, his father 1823-1828 (Box 3)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1824 (Box 3)
- Henry Bruce to James C. Bruce--Bound 1824-1855 (Box 3)
- James Bruce to Charles B. Williams November 25, 1825 (Box 3)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1825 (Box 3)
- Commonplace Book of James Coles Bruce ca. 1825-1829 (Box 3)
  Principally historical notes
- Elvira A. Bruce from James C. Bruce March 6, 1826 (Box 3)
- Charles B. Williams from James Bruce April 21, 1826 (Box 3)
- F.T. Anderson from Alexander Caruthers November 10, 1826 (Box 3)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1826-1827, 2 folders (Box 3)
- James Bruce to George Pannill & George Pannill to James Bruce January 15, 1828 & July 16, 1828 (Box 4)
- James C. Bruce to John S. Pendleton February 15, 1828 (Box 4)
- Charles B. Williams to James Bruce February 19, 1828 (Box 4)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1828 (Box 4)
- James C. Bruce from Mary P. Govan November 1, 1829 (Box 4)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1829 (Box 4)
- Mary [__________] from James C. Bruce January 3, 1830 (Box 4)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1830 (Box 4)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1831 (Box 4)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1831 (Box 4)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1831 (Box 4)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1832 (Box 4)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1832 (Box 4)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1832 (Box 4)
- "My Dear Aunt" from James C. Bruce December 19, 1833 (Box 4)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1833 (Box 4)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1833 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Mildred H. Carrington from Eliza Bruce January 22, 1834 (Box 5)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1834 (Box 5)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1834 (Box 5)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1834 (Box 5)
- James C. Bruce to James C. Bruce, his son June 11, 1835 (Box 5)
- Eliza Bruce from John Wilkins September 13, 1835 (Box 5)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1835 (Box 5)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1835 (Box 5)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1835 (Box 5)
- James C. Bruce to James S. Easley March 18, 1836 (Box 5)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1836 (Box 5)
- William Alexander Correspondence 1836 (Box 5)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1836 (Box 5)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1836 (Box 5)
- Thomas and Richard Bruce from James C. Bruce March 21, 1837 (Box 5)
- Eliza Bruce from M.H. Carrington June 7, 1837 (Box 5)
- Henry Bruce from Samuel Pannell November 27, 1837 (Box 5)
- James C. Bruce from G. Cooke December 11, 1837 (Box 5)
- Mary Elizabeth A. Bruce from Mrs. M.A. Anderson December 30, 1837 (Box 5)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1837 (Box 5)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1837 (Box 6)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1837, 2 folders (Box 6)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1837 (Box 6)
- Mary Evelyn Anderson from [_________] January 6, 1838 (Box 6)
- Bishop William Meade to Rev. Charles Draper March 5, 1838 (Box 6)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1838 (Box 6)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1838 (Box 6)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1838 (Box 6)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1838 (Box 7)
- Eliza Bruce from W.W. Wilkins April 14, 1839 (Box 7)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1839 (Box 7)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1839 (Box 7)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1839 (Box 7)
- Political Letter of James C. Bruce July 14, 1840 (Box 7)
- James C. Bruce to Lawrenceville Committee 1840 (Box 7)
- W. East Snowden to James C. Bruce 1840 (Box 7)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1840 (Box 7)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1840 (Box 8)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1840 (Box 8)
- Journal of Mrs. James Coles Bruce's Trip To New York ca. 1840, 2 volumes (Box 8)
- Eliza Bruce from Ann Green February 13, 1841 (Box 8)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1841, 3 folders (Box 8)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1841 (Box 8)
- Eliza Bruce Correspondence 1842 (Box 8)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1842 (Box 8)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1842 (Box 9)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1842 (Box 9)
- Elvira A. Bruce, his mother, to James C. Bruce January 24, 1843 (Box 9)
- Eliza Bruce Correspondence 1843 (Box 9)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1843, 2 folders (Box 9)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1843 (Box 9)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1844 (Box 10)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1844 (Box 10)
- James C. Bruce from Eliza Bruce 1844 (Box 10)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1844 (Box 10)
- Accounts of James Bruce 1844 (Box 10)
- James C. Bruce from Eliza Bruce January 6, 1845 (Box 10)
- Mrs. Eliza Bruce from Sally Bruce March 31, 1845 (Box 10)
- Miss Sally Brodnax from Eliza Bruce September 5, 1845 (Box 10)
- James C. Bruce from Sally Bruce September 31, 1845 (Box 10)
- Charles Bruce to James C. Bruce October 23, 1845 (Box 10)
- James C. Bruce from Eliza Bruce 1845 (Box 10)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce 1845 (Box 10)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1845, 2 folders (Box 10)
- Mrs. F.T. Anderson from Mr. F.T. Anderson December 23, 1846 (Box 11)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1846 (Box 11)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1846 (Box 11)
- Address delivered by James C. Bruce at Buffalo Springs July 4, 1847 (Box 11)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1847 (Box 11)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1847 (Box 11)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce August 8, 1848 (Box 11)
- Miss Catherine Carrington from Sally Brodnax November 3, 1848 (Box 11)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1848 (Box 11)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1846 (Box 11)
- Address Delivered by James C. Bruce at Buffalo Springs July 4, 1847 (Box 11)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1847 (Box 11)
- Accounts of James C. Bruce 1847 (Box 11)
- Eliza Bruce from James C. Bruce August 8, 1848 (Box 11)
- Miss Catherine Carrington from Sally Brodnax November 3, 1848 (Box 11)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1848 (Box 11)
- [___________] from W.B. Seddon April 19, 1849 (Box 11)
- List and Inventory of the Negroes on the Plantation of Messrs. Bruce, Seddon and Williams November 22, 1849 (Box 11)
- Miss Catherine Carrington from Sally Brodnax December 30, 1849 (Box 11)
- Eliza Bruce Correspondence 1849 (Box 11)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1849 (Box 12)
- List and Inventory of the Negroes on the Plantation of Messrs. Bruce, Seddon and Williams 1849 (Box 12)
- Mrs. James C. Bruce to Eliza Douglas Bruce February 27, 1850 (Box 12)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1850 (Box 12)
- Miss Catherine Carrington from Sally Brodnax 1850 (Box 12)
- Alexander Bruce from James C. Bruce 1850 (Box 12)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1850 (Box 12)
- Poem by [______] 1850 (Box 12)
- James C. Bruce from Sally Brodnax January 20, 1851 (Box 12)
- Mrs. Sarah E. Carrington from James C. Bruce April 29, 1851 (Box 12)
- Alexander Bruce from James C. Bruce 1851 (Box 12)
- James C. Bruce to his sons at V.M.I. 1851 (Box 12)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1851 (Box 12)
- Inventory of Household Ware, etc. 1851 (Box 12)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from Mrs. M.A. Anderson July 10, 1852 (Box 12)
- Mrs. M.A. Anderson from A.A. Anderson August 13, 1852 (Box 12)
- Alexander Bruce from James C. Bruce 1852 (Box 12)
- James C. to his sons at V.M.I.
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1852 (Box 12)
- Registers of Negroes 1852 (Box 13)
- Copy of the Last Will of James C. Bruce December 21, 1853 (Box 13)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1853 (Box 13)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1853 (Box 13)
- Charles Bruce from Alexander Bruce February 10, 1854 (Box 13)
- Wilkins Bruce from James C. Bruce August 19, 1854 (Box 13)
- Fanny Anderson from F.T. Anderson October 29, 1854 (Box 13)
- "My Dear Friend" [Alexander Bruce?] from Mary Evelyn Anderson December 16, 1854 (Box 13)
- Alexander Bruce from James C. Bruce 1854 (Box 13)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1854 (Box 13)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1854 (Box 13)
- Life Membership of James C. Bruce in Union Agricultural Society February 17, 1855 (Box 13)
- Judge Francis Thomas Anderson from Mary Evelyn Anderson Bruce June 9, 1855 (Box 13)
- Last Will and Testament of Henry Bruce July 23, 1855 (Box 13)
- Anne Anderson from Francis T. Anderson September 22, 1855 (Box 13)
- James C. Bruce to "My Dear Badard" November 12, 1855 (Box 13)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1855 (Box 13)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1855 (Box 13)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1855 (Box 13)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1856 (Box 14)
- Alexander Bruce from James C. Bruce 1856 (Box 14)
- James C. Bruce and Richard Bruce Correspondence 1856 (Box 14)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1856 (Box 14)
- James Bruce to "Sandy" October 14, 1857 (Box 14)
- James C. Bruce from Mary E. Bruce November 18, 1857 (Box 14)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1857 (Box 14)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1857 (Box 14)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1857 (Box 14)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1858 (Box 14)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1858 (Box 14)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1858 (Box 14)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1858 (Box 14)
- James C. Bruce from William Pannell February 18, 1859 (Box 15)
- Charles Bruce from James C. Bruce March 29, 1859 (Box 15)
- Alexander Bruce from James C. Bruce November 19, 1859 (Box 15)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1859 (Box 15)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1859, 2 folders (Box 15)
- Cad Jones to James C. Bruce March 7, 1860 (Box 15)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1860 (Box 15)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1860 (Box 15)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1860 (Box 15)
- Mrs. M.A. Anderson from W. Alex Anderson July 27, 1861 (Box 15)
- Alexander Bruce to "Charly" November 10, 1861 (Box 15)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from W. Anderson December 11, 1861 (Box 15)
- John A. Gennett from Alexander Bruce December 27, 1861 (Box 15)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1861 (Box 15)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1861 (Box 15)
- Charles Bruce Correspondence 1861 (Box 15)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1861 (Box 15)
- Charles Bruce to James C. Bruce January 3, 1862 (Box 16)
- James C. Bruce from Charles Bruce June 2 [1862] (Box 16)
- Major [___________] from Chas. S. Carrington November 27, 1862 (Box 16)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1862 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1862 (Box 16)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence 1862 (Box 16)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1862 (Box 16)
- F.T. Anderson from Mary Evelyn Bruce January 7, 1863 (Box 16)
- Mr. George M. Williams from James C. Bruce April 21, 1863 (Box 16)
- James C. Bruce from Edmund Wilkins May 28, 1863 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from Josephine Anderson July 19, 1863 (Box 16)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1863 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1863 (Box 16)
- Business Papers of James C. Bruce 1863 (Box 16)
- Frank Anderson from Mrs. M.A. Anderson January, 1864 (Box 16)
- Halifax County Bonds July 25, 1864 (Box 16)
- James C. Bruce from William B. Bruce December 28, 1864 (Box 16)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1864 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1864 (Box 16)
- Business Papers of James C. and Alex Bruce 1864 (Box 16)
- Alexander Bruce from Francis T. Anderson January 25, 1865 (Box 16)
- Articles of Agreement between Wilkins Bruce and Alexander Bruce December 13, 1865 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1865 (Box 16)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1865 (Box 16)
- Alexander Bruce from W.D. Blair & Co. February 13, 1866 (Box 16)
- Business Papers of WIlliam Ballard Bruce November 15, 1866 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1866 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1866 (Box 16)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1866 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1867 (Box 16)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1867 (Box 16)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1867 (Box 16)
- John S. Pendleton from Alexander Bruce October 8, 1868 (Box 16)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1868 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1868 (Box 16)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1868 (Box 16)
- "My Dear Littel Scholar" from Fannie Anderson August 9, 1869 (Box 16)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1869 (Box 16)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1869 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1870 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1870 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1871 (Box 17)
- Alexander Bruce from [___________] March 5, 1872 (Box 17)
- Fannie Anderson from William A. Anderson May 16, 1872 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1872 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1874 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1875 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1876 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from Mrs. M.A. Anderson July 15, 1877 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1877 (Box 17)
- Mr. Alexander Bruce from Mary A. Bruce June 28, 1878 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from F.T. Anderson November 24, 1878 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from William A. Anderson 1878 (Box 17)
- Business Prospecters 1878 (Box 1878)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1878-1879 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce fom Mrs. M.A. Anderson February 19, 1879 (Box 17)
- Statement of Account of John B. McPhail with William B. Bruce 1880 (Box 17)
- Alexander Bruce from F.T. Anderson February 26, 1881 (Box 17)
- "In Memoriam"--Mrs. Mary Anne Anderson November 27, 1881 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from Fanny N. Anderson December 7,1882 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from C.F. Johnson December 12, 1882 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from Francis T. Anderson May 27, 1883 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1883 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce February 6, 1884 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1884 (Box 17)
- Mary Bruce from W.C. Bruce 1884-1885 (Box 17)
- Ellen Bruce from W.C. Bruce 1884-1885 (Box 17)
- Walter Bruce to "My Dear Cousin" December 18, 1885 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1885 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1885 (Box 17)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence 1886 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1886 (Box 17)
- Business Correspondence to William Ballard Bruce January 19, 1887 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1888 (Box 17)
- Alexander Bruce from E. Bruce September 4, 1889 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1889 (Box 17)
- Alexander Bruce from Charles Bruce October 23, 1890 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce and Marie M. Bruce 1890 (Box 17)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1891 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1891 (Box 18)
- Mrs. Pendleton from Mary Evelyn Bruce March 30, 1892 (Box 18)
- Mr. Pendleton from Alexander Bruce April 11, 1892 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1892 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1892 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1893 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1893 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1894 (Box 18)
- W.A. Bruce to [Alexander Bruce] June 25, 1895
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1895 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1895 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1895 (Box 18)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1896 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1896 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1896 (Box 18)
- Alexander Bruce from George M. Williams May 18, 1897 (Box 18)
- Fannie Anderson from Janetta Alexander December 26, 1897 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1897 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1897 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1898 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of William Ballard Bruce 1898 (Box 18)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence 1899 (Box 18)
- Correspondence from Administration of the University of Virginia accepting gift of books to Library to Malcolm G. Bruce 1899 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of Alexander Bruce 1899 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of Bruce Family 1899 (Box 18)
- Business Papers of Bruce Family 1900-1904, 5 folders (Box 19)
- Business Papers of Marie M. Bruce 1905 (Box 19)
- Fragments of Bruce Business Papers ca. 1800-1900 (Box 19)
- Miscellaneous Bruce Papers ca. 1800-1900 (Box 19)
- Eliza Bruce from A. Fontaine February 7, ________ (Box 19)
- Francis Anderson from Josephine Anderson February 21, _________ (Box 19)
- Maria Bruce to her father n.d. (Box 19)
- Alexander Bruce from Mary Evelyn Bruce n.d. (Box 19)
- Alexander Bruce from Sarah Bruce Seddon n.d. (Box 19)
- "My dearest Belle" from Josephine Anderson n.d. (Box 19)
- James C. Bruce from Mildred H. Carrington n.d. (Box 19)
- Alexander Bruce Correspondence n.d. (Box 19)
- Charles Bruce to James C. Bruce n.d. (Box 19)
- Ellen Bruce from Malcolm G. Bruce n.d. (Box 19)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from Josephine Anderson n.d. (Box 19)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from Fanny Anderson n.d. (Box 19)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from Alexander Bruce n.d. (Box 19)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from Anna Anderson n.d. (Box 19)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce from H.N. Bascom n.d. (Box 19)
- Mary Evelyn Bruce Correspondence n.d. (Box 19)
- Eliza Bruce Correspondence n.d. (Box 19)
- James C. Bruce Correspondence n.d. (Box 19)
- Papers of the Bruce Family n.d. (Box 19)
- Business Papers of James C. and Alexander Bruce n.d. (Box 20)
- Miscellaneous Bruce Papers n.d. (Box 20)
- Sketches in Bruce Papers n.d. (Box 20)
- History of Charlotte County and Bruce Estate n.d. (Box 20)
- Photographs in Bruce Collection n.d. (Box 20)
- Genealogical Material n.d. (Box 20)
- Manuscripts for Novel by Alexander Bruce n.d. (Box 21)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles in Bruce Papers n.d. (Box 21)
- Miscellaneous Papers from William Ballard Bruce Papers n.d. (Box 21)
- "The Missing Link," a Detective Story n.d. (Box 21)